commarts.com 2008-12-17

# Communication Arts Privacy Policy

Last revised: January 9, 2008

**_Communication Arts_ and www.commarts.com are owned and operated by:  
**Coyne & Blanchard, Inc.  
110 Constitution Dr  
Menlo Park, CA 94025  
(650) 326-6040

* * *

###  Introduction

It's our goal to bring you information that's valuable to your career and, at the same time, protect your privacy. Since we want you to feel comfortable using our site, please familiarize yourself with the following policy.

Your use of any portion of the _Communication Arts_ Web site means that you agree to the terms of our policy as it is outlined below. If you cannot agree with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Web site. This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time; the date of the most recent revision will appear at the top of this page. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check this page periodically. Continued access of this Web site by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy. 

* * *

###  The Type of Information We Collect 

We collect the e-mail addresses of anyone who communicates with us via e-mail, as well as any information volunteered by you, including survey information, name and address, telephone number, payment information (e.g., credit card number and billing address), etc.

Our servers may also automatically collect information about your computer when you visit our Web site, including the type of browser software you use, the operating system you are running, the Web site that referred you, and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, which is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet.

* * *

###  How We Use the Information Provided by You

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our site, customize the content and/or layout for each individual visitor and to contact you for marketing purposes. For example, if you subscribe to our publication, we may use your e-mail address to send you a confirmation notice and/or your mailing address to send you the publication. Similarly, if you enter our competitions, we may use this information to notify you if you are a winner. We may also use the information to communicate with you about new features, products or services, and/or to improve the services that we offer by tailoring them to your needs.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders that have been placed on-line.

If you supply us with your postal address online you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services. 

* * *

###  Cookies 

We use cookies to store your preferences, record session information, such as items that you add to your shopping cart, ensure that you are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads and customize Web page content based on your browser type.

* * *

###  Ad Servers

To try and bring you information that might be of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web site. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of [www.doubleclick.com](http://www.doubleclick.com/ "Double Click"). 

* * *

###  Security

The personal information that you provide in connection with ordering products or services from _Communication Arts_ is protected in several ways:

Access to this information is available to you through a unique user name and password. The password is encrypted and we recommend that you not divulge it to anyone. In addition, your registration information resides on a secure server that only selected _Communication Arts_ personnel have access to.

When you use your charge card online, your personal details and credit card information are scrambled using SSL encryption technology before being sent over the Internet. Although we cannot guarantee encryption or the privacy of your personal details and credit card information, SSL makes it very difficult for your information to be stolen or intercepted while being transferred.

* * *

###  Opting Out/Discontinuation

Your privacy is important to us. If you do not want to receive communication from us in the future, please contact us at the address listed above and we will make sure to remove you from our mailing list.

* * *

###  Contact Us

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, the practices of _Communication Arts_ , your dealings with us or just want to give us feedback or suggestions, please contact us at the address listed above.

If you believe that we have not complied with our Privacy Policy, with respect to your personal information, please contact us at the above address. In your communication, describe in as much detail as possible the ways in which you believe that we have not complied with our policy and we will investigate your complaint.
